A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative Files, 1922-2004; 1
  - Officer and Committee Files, 1922-1998; 2
    - Officer Files, 1922-1998; A
      - Marianna O. Lewis, 1945-1982; 7
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 4, 1967-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 386)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 4 - Index Problems, undated (Reel 55, Frame 451)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 4 - Publicity, 1971-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 455)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 4 - Reactions, 1971-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 507)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 5, 1973 (Reel 55, Frame 560)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 5 - Pending, 1974-1975 (Reel 55, Frame 576)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 6, 1977 (Reel 55, Frame 606)
        - The Foundation Directory - Edition 8 - Direct Mailing, 1981 (Reel 55, Frame 615)
        - The Foundation Library Center - Consulting Services, 1963-1967 (Reel 55, Frame 623)
        - The Foundation Library Center - Directory, 1957-1961 (Reel 55, Frame 637)
        - The Foundation Library Center - 990-A Control REcord, 1963-1970 (Reel 55, Frame 701)
        - Foundation Names from Telephone Inquiries, 1958-1967 (Reel 55, Frame 763)
        - Foundation News, 1960-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 789)
        - Foundation Personnel Study, 1968-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 856)
        - Foundation Project Reports, 1975-1977 (Reel 55, Frame 874)
        - Foundation Reports, 1959-1978 (Reel 55, Frame 974)
        - Foundation Self-Regulation and Accountability, 1970-1979 (Reel 55, Frame 1,050)
        - Foundation Statistics, 1962-1975 (Reel 55, Frame 1,123)
        - Foundation Stock Offerings, 1972-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 1,210)
        - Gardner Commission, 1970 (Reel 55, Frame 1,255)
        - Grants Index, 1966 (Reel 56, Frame 1)
        - Grants Index - Grants Data Bank, 1972-1973 (Reel 56, Frame 12)
        - Information Quarterly 2-1, 1973 (Reel 56, Frame 27)
        - Information Quarterly 2-2, 1973 (Reel 56, Frame 35)
        - Information Quarterly 2-3, 1973-1974 (Reel 56, Frame 38)
        - Information Quarterly 2-4, 1974 (Reel 56, Frame 49)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Data Bank Projects, 1974-1978 (Reel 56, Frame 70)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Depository, 1972-1978 (Reel 56, Frame 154)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Distribution of the Internal Revenue Service Films, 1972 (Reel 56, Frame 179)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Exempt Organizations Master File (EOMF), 1979 (Reel 56, Frame 217)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Forms, undated (Reel 56, Frame 227)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Meeting, June 1975, 1974-1975 (Reel 56, Frame 238)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Meeting, February 20, 1976 (Reel 56, Frame 296)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Meeting, June 2, 1976 (Reel 56, Frame 323)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1957-1967 (Reel 56, Frame 354)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Microfilm Project, 1971-1972 (Reel 56, Frame 460)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Procedures for Transcribing Form 990-A, 1958-1960 (Reel 56, Frame 515)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Reports by Marianna Olmstead, 1957-1961 (Reel 56, Frame 542)
        - Internal Revenue Service - Washington, D. C., 1961-1981 (Reel 56, Frame 624)
        - Internal Revenue Service Center, 1963-1981 (Reel 56, Frame 804)
        - Library Visitors, 1958-1960 (Reel 56, Frame 1,049)
        - List of Foundations, 1958-1963 (Reel 56, Frame 1,077)
        - Mark-Martin Associates, 1980-1981 (Reel 56, Frame 1,128)
        - Master Tables and Foundation Charts, undated (Reel 57, Frame 1)
        - National Institute of Health - Draft Report on Foundation Spending, 1975 (Reel 57, Frame 170)
        - New York University - The Eighth Biennial Conference on Charitable Foundations, May 15-16, 1967 (Reel 57, Frame 195)
        - 1973 Data Bank Project, 1974-1975 (Reel 57, Frame 355)
        - Pending, 1970-1977 (Reel 57, Frame 389)
        - Quarterly Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Reel 57, Frame 503)
        - Patricia Read, 1981-1982 (Reel 57, Frame 520)
        - Regional Collections, 1972-1978 (Reel 57, Frame 668)
        - Research Projects, 1968-1977 (Reel 57, Frame 851)
        - Commission on Foundations and Private Philanthropy (Rockefeller Commission), 1969-1970 (Reel 57, Frame 924)
        - William Ruiz, 1981-1982 (Reel 57, Frame 983)
        - Special Inquiries to Marianna O. Lewis, 1967-1981 (Reel 57, Frame 994)
        - Standards for Foundations, 1969-1970 (Reel 57, Frame 1,125)
        - Statistics and Analyses, 1971-1978 (Reel 57, Frame 1,153)
        - Status of Community Foundations, 1975 (Reel 58, Frame 1)
        - A Study of Systems and Procedures for The Foundation Center, 1975 (Reel 58, Frame 32)
      - Nathaniel Spear III, 1969-1974; 8
        Nathaniel Spear III worked as the international specialist (1969-1974) for The Foundation Center.
        - Nathaniel Spear III - International Specialist, 1969-1974 (Reel 58, Frame 60)
      - Trustees (Deceased), 1955-1998; 9
        Series 1.2A.9 is labeled "Deceased Trustees." At the time of filming many of these Trustees were not yet deceased. The material was originally labeled in this way because many of the trustees had passed away; but several of the trustees mentioned (such as Vernon Jordan) were placed in the category of "deceased" after declining to accept a Trustee Emeritus position with the Center.
        This series contains correspondence and newspaper clippings about The Foundation Center's trustees.
        - Charles W. Bailey II, 1973-1982 (Reel 58, Frame 237)
        - Geno Ballotti, 1982-1984 (Reel 58, Frame 247)
        - Harding F. Bancroft, 1973-1992 (Reel 58, Frame 273)
        - Robert C. Bates, 1963-1991 (Reel 58, Frame 292)
        - Wilbur J. Bender, 1968-1969 (Reel 58, Frame 359)
        - Anthony A. Bliss, 1974-1991 (Reel 58, Frame 384)
        - Landrum R. Bolling, 1975-1981 (Reel 58, Frame 401)
        - Julian P. Boyd, 1956-1971 (Reel 58, Frame 424)
        - William A. Buzick, Jr., 1972-1982 (Reel 58, Frame 591)
        - John B. Coburn, 1971-1973 (Reel 58, Frame 676)
        - Fred C. Cole, 1971-1986 (Reel 58, Frame 683)
        - Morris D. Crawford, 1963-1970 (Reel 58, Frame 830)
        - Merrimon Cunninggim, 1963-1995 (Reel 58, Frame 913)
        - G. Harold Duling, 1961-1965 (Reel 58, Frame 1,032)
        - William C. Greenough, 1961-1990 (Reel 58, Frame 1,129)
        - J. George Harrar, 1970-1982 (Reel 59, Frame 1)
        - Fred H. Harrington, 1968-1995 (Reel 59, Frame 24)
        - Rembrandt C. Hiller, Jr., 1962-1977 (Reel 59, Frame 38)
        - James Kimball Johnson II, 1956-1969 (Reel 59, Frame 128)
        - George S. Johnston, 1975-1991 (Reel 59, Frame 272)
        - Boisfeuillet Jones, 1975-2001 (Reel 59, Frame 327)
        - Vernon Jordan, 1971-1998 (Reel 59, Frame 369)
        - Wilbur K. Jordan, 1961-1971 (Reel 59, Frame 387)
        - John G. Kemeny, 1970-1991 (Reel 59, Frame 452)
        - John A. Krout, 1956-1979 (Reel 59, Frame 472)
        - W. McNeil Lowry, 1969-1991 (Reel 59, Frame 526)
        - Robert J. McCracken, 1956-1973 (Reel 59, Frame 551)
        - Deaderick C. Montague, 1983-1992 (Reel 59, Frame 613)
        - Emory W. Morris, 1956-1987 (Reel 59, Frame 645)
        - Robert H. Mulreany, 1989-1998 (Reel 59, Frame 739)
        - Vernon Munroe, Jr., 1956-1969 (Reel 59, Frame 775)
        - James A. Perkins, 1955-1998 (Reel 59, Frame 833)
        - Gordon N. Ray, 1962-1986 (Reel 60, Frame 1)
        - Frank A. Saunders, 1982-1990 (Reel 60, Frame 231)
        - Sydney Stein, Jr., 1964-1991 (Reel 60, Frame 282)
        - J. Tyson Stokes, 1963-1980 (Reel 60, Frame 316)
        - Richard H. Sullivan, 1967-1976 (Reel 60, Frame 384)
        - Robert L. Sutherland, 1956-1979 (Reel 60, Frame 513)
        - Alexander B. Trowbridge, 1973-1991 (Reel 60, Frame 688)
        - Walter M. Upchurch, Jr., 1958-1970 (Reel 60, Frame 706)
        - Edwin H. Vause, 1971-1973 (Reel 60, Frame 817)
        - Homer C. Wadsworth, 1978-1994 (Reel 60, Frame 829)
        - Martha R. Wallace, 1971-1989 (Reel 60, Frame 922)
        - Sidney J. Weinberg, Jr., 1971-1974 (Reel 60, Frame 1,069)
        - Herbert B. West, 1975-1990 (Reel 61, Frame 1)
        - John D. Wilson, 1956-1967 (Reel 61, Frame 422)
        - Bernard Wolfman, 1970-1976 (Reel 61, Frame 447)
        - John E. F. Wood, 1956-1969 (Reel 61, Frame 471)
        - William R. Wright, 1971-1975 (Reel 61, Frame 499)
        - Donald R. Young, 1956-1977 (Reel 61, Frame 504)
        - Arnold J. Zurcher, 1961-1974 (Reel 61, Frame 555)
    - Committee Files, 1967-1994; B
      This series contains correspondence, minutes, and agenda of various large committees in The Foundation Center: the Board of Trustees, the Executive Committee, and the Finance and Audit Committee.
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Reel 61, Frame 651)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1985 (Reel 61, Frame 656)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1986 (Reel 61, Frame 721)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1987 (Reel 61, Frame 787)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1988 (Reel 61, Frame 889)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1989 (Reel 61, Frame 1,006)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1990 (Reel 61, Frame 1,027)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1991 (Reel 61, Frame 1,051)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Reel 61, Frame 1,083)
      - Board of Trustees - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Reel 61, Frame 1,119)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 3, 1967 (Reel 62, Frame 1)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 26, 1969 (Reel 62, Frame 29)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, October 21, 1971 (Reel 62, Frame 68)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 10, 1972 (Reel 62, Frame 209)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, October 26, 1972 (Reel 62, Frame 257)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 26, 1973 (Reel 62, Frame 296)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, October 31, 1973 (Reel 62, Folder 310)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 23, 1974 (Reel 62, Frame 510)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 2, 1974 (Reel 62, Frame 572)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 4, 1974 (Reel 62, Frame 579)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 1, 1975 (Reel 62, Frame 676)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 11, 1975 (Reel 62, Frame 811)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 21, 1976 (Reel 62, Frame 894)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, October 28, 1976 (Reel 62, Frame 1,047)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 12, 1977 (Reel 63, Frame 1)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 10, 1977 (Reel 63, Frame 90)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 11, 1978 (Reel 63, Frame 101)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 9, 1978 (Reel 63, Frame 123)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 10, 1979 (Reel 63, Frame 180)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 8, 1979 (Reel 63, Frame 223)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 15, 1980 (Reel 63, Frame 250)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 13, 1980 (Reel 63, Frame 284)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, April 30, 1981 (Reel 63, Frame 310)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 21, 1981 (Reel 63, Frame 334)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 13, 1982 (Reel 63, Frame 367)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 16, 1982 (Reel 63, Frame 425)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 12, 1983 (Reel 63, Frame 492)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 22, 1983 (Reel 63, Frame 561)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 15, 1984 (Reel 63, Frame 614)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 15, 1984 (Reel 63, Frame 661)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 23, 1985 (Reel 63, Frame 734)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 14, 1985 (Reel 63, Frame 870)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 13, 1986 (Reel 63, Frame 955)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 21, 1986 (Reel 63, Frame 1,059)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 12, 1987 (Reel 63, Frame 1,152)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 20, 1987 (Reel 64, Frame 1)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 17, 1988 (Reel 64, Frame 66)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 22, 1988 (Reel 64, Frame 156)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, February 21, 1989 (Reel 64, Frame 192)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 16, 1989 (Reel 64, Frame 208)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 21, 1989 (Reel 64, Frame 309)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 15, 1990 (Reel 64, Frame 348)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 20, 1990 (Reel 64, Frame 446)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 14, 1991 (Reel 64, Frame 510)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 19, 1991 (Reel 64, Frame 563)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 12, 1992 (Reel 64, Frame 634)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 17, 1992 (Reel 64, Frame 720)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 18, 1993 (Reel 64, Frame 822)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 16, 1993 (Reel 64, Frame 896)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, May 17, 1994 (Reel 64, Frame 941)
      - Board of Trustees - Meetings/Minutes, November 15, 1994 (Reel 64, Frame 1,004)
      - Board of Trustees - Memoranda, 1977-1979 (Reel 64, Frame 1,072)
      - Board of Trustees - Progress Reports, 1974-1976 (Reel 64, Frame 1,112)
      - Board of Trustees - 30th Anniversary Luncheon, November 21, 1986 (Reel 65, Frame 1)
      - Board of Trustees - Year End Reports, 1987 (Reel 65, Frame 119)
      - Board of Trustees - Mid-Year Report, 1988 (Reel 65, Frame 136)
      - Board of Trustees - Year End Reports, 1988 (Reel 65, Frame 164)
      - Board of Trustees - Mid-Year Report, 1989 (Reel 65, Frame 201)
      - Board of Trustees - Year End Reports, 1989 (Reel 65, Frame 232)
      - Board of Trustees - Mid-Year Report, 1990 (Reel 65, Frame 272)
      - Board of Trustees - Year End Reports, 1990 (Reel 65, Frame 308)
      - Board of Trustees - Mid-Year Report, 1991 (Reel 65, Frame 348)
      - Board of Trustees - Year End Reports, 1991 (Reel 65, Frame 374)
      - Corporate Services Committee, 1978-1982 (Reel 65, Frame 417)
      - DeMarche Associates Reports, 1983 (Reel 65, Frame 625)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, November 2, 1973 (Reel 65, Frame 674)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 9, 1974 (Reel 65, Frame 677)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 8, 1974 (Reel 65, Frame 730)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 7, 1975 (Reel 65, Frame 805)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 9, 1975 (Reel 65, Frame 874)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, March 23, 1976 (Reel 65, Frame 909)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, September 30, 1976 (Reel 65, Frame 935)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 13, 1977 (Reel 65, Frame 979)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 13, 1977 (Reel 65, Frame 989)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 12, 1978 (Reel 65, Frame 1,017)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 12, 1978 (Reel 65, Frame 1,024)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 12, 1979 (Reel 65, Frame 1,028)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 12, 1979 (Reel 65, Frame 1,034)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 18, 1980 (Reel 65, Frame 1,038)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 16, 1980 (Reel 65, Frame 1,043)
      - Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 16, 1981 (Reel 65, Frame 1,046)
      - Executive Committee - Special Meeting, January 11, 1984 (Reel 65, Frame 1,049)
      - Executive Committee - Special Meeting, May 22, 1984 (Reel 65, Frame 1,065)
      - Finance Committee - Meetings/Minutes, March 29, 1974 (Reel 65, Frame 1,085)
      - Finance Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 8, 1974 (Reel 65, Frame 1,090)
      - Finance Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 7, 1975 (Reel 65, Frame 1,094)
      - Finance Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 6, 1975 (Reel 65, Frame 1,113)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, September 28, 1976 (Reel 65, Frame 1,134)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 13, 1977 (Reel 66, Frame 1)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 12, 1978 (Reel 66, Frame 49)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 12, 1978 (Reel 66, Frame 54)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 12, 1979 (Reel 66, Frame 60)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 12, 1979 (Reel 66, Frame 67)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 18, 1980 (Reel 66, Frame 74)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 16, 1980 (Reel 66, Frame 81)
      - Finance and Audit Committee - Special Meeting, May 26, 1986 (Reel 66, Frame 88)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Correspondence, 1987 (Reel 66, Frame 91)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 16, 1981 (Reel 66, Frame 100)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, November 3, 1981 (Reel 66, Frame 130)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 5, 1982 (Reel 66, Frame 163)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 12, 1982 (Reel 66, Frame 191)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, February 11, 1983 (Reel 66, Frame 237)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 28, 1983 (Reel 66, Frame 302)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, November 10, 1983 (Reel 66, Frame 388)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 19, 1984 (Reel 66, Frame 426)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 29, 1984 (Reel 66, Frame 453)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 18, 1985 (Reel 66, Frame 482)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 15, 1985 (Reel 66, Frame 499)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 17, 1986 (Reel 66, Frame 576)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 16, 1986 (Reel 66, Frame 641)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 16, 1987 (Reel 66, Frame 769)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, November 5, 1987 (Reel 66, Frame 820)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, February 2, 1988 (Reel 66, Frame 917)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 21, 1988 (Reel 66, Frame 968)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 20, 1988 (Reel 66, Frame 1,007)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 18, 1989 (Reel 66, Frame 1,025)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 23, 1989 (Reel 66, Frame 1,061)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 24, 1990 (Reel 66, Frame 1,087)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 23, 1990 (Reel 66, Frame 1,134)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, May 1, 1991 (Reel 67, Frame 1)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 23, 1991 (Reel 67, Frame 101)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 14, 1992 (Reel 67, Frame 170)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 19, 1992 (Reel 67, Frame 253)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 20, 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 350)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 13, 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 434)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, April 14, 1994 (Reel 67, Frame 488)
      - Finance and Audit Committee and Executive Committee - Meetings/Minutes, October 21, 1994 (Reel 67, Frame 536)
      - Fund Development Committee, 1990-1991 (Reel 67, Frame 575)
      - Fund-Raising Committee and Executive Committee, May 22, 1986 (Reel 67, Frame 708)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1980-1982 (Reel 67, Frame 751)
      - Nominating Committee, 1960-1981 (Reel 67, Frame 939)
      - Nominating Committee, 1982-1987 (Reel 67, Frame 1,100)
- Program and Project Files, 1924-1999; 2
  Series 2 is arranged in two subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Programs
  Subseries 2 - Special Projects
  - Programs, 1924-1998; 1
    Series 2.1 is arranged in 6 sections:
    A - Associates Program Files
    B - Donor Files
    C - Foundation Correspondence
    D - Programs
    E - Prospects
    F - Sponsors
    Information in Series 2.1 is primarily centered around financial material and fund-raising that The Foundation Center actively pursued.
    - Associates Program Files, 1975-1997; A
      The Associates Program is a fee-based program. Being a member of the Associates Program gave an organization the opportunity to use the resources of The Foundation Center for a small fee on top of the yearly fee. A primary benefit of membership was the ability to draw on the vast database The Foundation Center maintained.
      - Associate Files - Complete Listing, 1975-1997 (Reel 68, Frame 4)
      - Associate Files - Form LEtters, 1978-1987 (Reel 68, Frame 35)
      - Abilene Christian University, 1983-1986 (Reel 68, Frame 46)
      - AIDS Resource Center, 1990 (Reel 68, Frame 49)
      - Air Service International, 1994 (Reel 68, Frame 56)
      - Albert Einstein Healthcare Foundation, 1992 (Reel 68, Frame 59)
      - Albright College, 1981 (Reel 68, Frame 61)
      - Alderson Broaddus College, 1988 (Reel 68, Frame 64)
      - Alfred University, 1989-1990 (Reel 68, Frame 66)
      - Allegheny College, 1985-1990 (Reel 68, Frame 74)
      - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1987 (Reel 68, Frame 78)
      - American City Bureau, 1989-1990 (Reel 68, Frame 80)
      - American Council for the Arts, 1991 (Reel 68, Frame 85)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1991 (Reel 68, Frame 87)
      - American Friends of Asaf Harofeh Medical Center, 1992-1993 (Reel 68, Frame 89)
      - American Friends of the Hebrew Museum, Inc., 1981-1987 (Reel 68, Frame 93)
      - American Geriatrics Society, 1994 (Reel 68, Frame 97)
      - American Law Institute, 1995 (Reel 68, Frame 99)
      - American Red Cross, Washington, D. C., 1992-1997 (Reel 68, Frame 101)
      - American University, 1985-1989 (Reel 68, Frame 107)
      - Arluck Entertainment, 1994 (Reel 68, Frame 113)
      - Arts and Communication Counselors, 1987 (Reel 68, Frame 118)